<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='../../ld2.xsl'?>
<LOBBYINGDISCLOSURE2>
   <imported>N</imported>
   <pages>10</pages>
   <submitURL></submitURL>
   <organizationName>NATIONAL COMMITTEE TO PRESERVE SOCIAL SECURITY AND MEDICARE</organizationName>
   <prefix></prefix>
   <firstName></firstName>
   <lastName></lastName>
   <registrantDifferentAddress>N</registrantDifferentAddress>
   <address1>10 G STREET, NE, #600</address1>
   <address2></address2>
   <city>WASHINGTON</city>
   <state>DC</state>
   <zip>20002</zip>
   <zipext></zipext>
   <country>USA</country>
   <principal_city></principal_city>
   <principal_state></principal_state>
   <principal_zip></principal_zip>
   <principal_zipext></principal_zipext>
   <principal_country></principal_country>
   <selfSelect>Y</selfSelect>
   <clientName>NATIONAL COMMITTEE TO PRESERVE SOCIAL SECURITY AND MEDICARE</clientName>
   <clientGovtEntity>N</clientGovtEntity>
   <senateID>27467-12</senateID>
   <houseID>303670000</houseID>
   <reportYear>2013</reportYear>
   <reportType>Q1</reportType>
   <terminationDate></terminationDate>
   <noLobbying></noLobbying>
   <income></income>
   <expenses>310000.00</expenses>
   <expensesMethod>A</expensesMethod>
   <printedName>Max Richtman, President and CEO</printedName>
   <signedDate>04/12/2013</signedDate>
   <alis>
      <ali_info>
         <issueAreaCode>BUD</issueAreaCode>
         <specific_issues>
            <description>President of the U.S. Fiscal Year (FY) 2014 Budget.  (No bill.)  Proposals pertaining to funding the Social Security Administration (SSA), Medicare, Older Americans Act programs, and the Low Income Home Energy Assistance Program, and a proposal to adopt the chained consumer price index (CPI) for the purpose of determining Social Security cost-of-living adjustments (COLA).</description>
            <description>FY 2014 Budget of the U.S.  H. Con. Res. 25; substitute amendments to H. Con. Res. 25; S. Con. Res. 8:  proposals for the FY 2014 budget including provisions pertaining to SSA administrative funding, Social Security, Medicare, Medicaid, Older Americans Act programs, the Low Income Home Energy Assistance Program, and amendments to S. Con. Res. 8 pertaining to the chained CPI and the Medicare premium support voucher.

Supplemental Unified Budget.  H.R. 444, the Require a Plan Act:  amendment calling for the utilization of the Simpson-Bowles Commission recommendations for the  establishment of the FY 2014 budget and to set forth the budgetary levels for FY 2015 through FY 2023.

Labor, Health and Human Services, and Education, and Related Agencies Fiscal Year 2014 Appropriations.  (No bill.)  Provisions appropriating funds for Older Americans Act programs, elderly falls prevention, and SSA administrative expenses.

Continuing Appropriations.  H.R. 933, the Consolidated and Further Continuing Appropriations Act of 2013:  provisions making continuing appropriations for FY 2013, including appropriations for SSA administrative funding.

Budget Control Act of 2011/Sequestration.  S. 388, the American Family Protection Act:  legislation eliminating the automatic spending reductions scheduled to occur under current law (P.L. 112-25) for 2013 and partially eliminating the reductions scheduled for 2014.

Fiscal Cliff Agreement.  H.R. 8 (112th Congress), the American Taxpayer Relief Act of 2012 (P.L. 112-240):  extending the Bush-era tax cuts for individuals earning more than $400,000 and couples earning more than $450,000.  
</description>
         </specific_issues>
         <federal_agencies>U.S. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES, U.S. SENATE, President of the U.S., Vice President of the U.S., Executive Office of the President (EOP), Office of Management &amp; Budget (OMB), Treasury - Dept of, Natl Economic Council (NEC)</federal_agencies>
         <lobbyists>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Max</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Richtman</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Dan</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Adcock</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Webster</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Phillips</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Diane</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Lifsey</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Brenda</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Sulick</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Julie</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Tippens</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition>Chief of Staff, Hon. Colleen Hanabusa</coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>Y</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
         </lobbyists>
         <foreign_entity_issues></foreign_entity_issues>
      </ali_info>
      <ali_info>
         <issueAreaCode>MMM</issueAreaCode>
         <specific_issues>
            <description>Medicare Benefit Redesign.  (No bill.)  Proposals to combine Part A and B deductibles along with a catastrophic cap on Medicare out-of-pocket spending to be paid for by increased out-of-pocket costs for Medicare beneficiaries.

</description>
            <description>Medicare Drug Savings. (No bill.)  Proposals to extend the application of Medicaid drug rebates to prescription drugs paid for by Medicare and used by people eligible for both Medicare and Medicaid (dual-eligibles), and by people receiving the Medicare Part D Low-Income Subsidy.

Medicare Home Health Benefits.  (No bill.)  Proposals pertaining to copayments for beneficiaries receiving the Medicare home health benefit.

Medicare Premium Support.  H. Con. Res. 25:  proposal to privatize Medicare.

Medicare Income-Relating.  H. Con. Res. 25:  proposals to increase the cost of Medicare to higher-income beneficiaries.

Medicare Eligibility Age.  H. Con. Res. 25:  proposals to increase the Medicare eligibility age.

Medicare Part D Negotiation of Drug Prices.  S. 117, S. 408, H.R. 1102, H.R. 928: proposals to create a Medicare-operated prescription drug plan, allowing or requiring the Secretary of the Department of Health and Human Services to negotiate price concessions from pharmaceutical manufacturers for drugs purchased under the Part D program.

Medicare Supplemental Health Insurance.  (No bill.)  Proposals to increase costs for Medicare beneficiaries who purchase Medigap insurance. 

Medicare Physician Fees.  (No bill.)  Proposals pertaining to a permanent fix of the sustainable growth rate (SGR) formula to determine physician fees under Part B. 

Medicare Observations Status.  S. 569, H.R. 1179:  legislation to count days in the hospital in observation status toward meeting the three-day prior hospitalization requirement for skilled nursing facility (SNF) care eligibility.

Comprehensive Health Care Reform.  P.L. 111-148, P.L. 111-152:  Implementation of provisions reducing Medicare Advantage plan payments; requiring higher income Medicare beneficiaries to pay an increased share of Medicare Parts B and D premium costs; expanding benefits for low-income beneficiaries under the Medicare Savings Programs and the Part D Low-Income Subsidy (LIS); expanding coverage of prevention services; establishing a Medicare Commission; providing expanded Medicaid coverage for home and community-based services; authorizing the collection of data regarding disparities in the provision of care; providing safeguards and subsidies to assure affordability of health coverage for seniors.

Center for Medicare and Medicaid Innovation.  (No bill.)  Proposals related to the planning for the Center for Medicare and Medicaid Innovations, and the approach the Center will take to test innovative payment and service delivery models to reduce program expenditures, while preserving or enhancing the quality of care for Medicare, Medicaid and CHIP beneficiaries.

Federal Coordinated Health Care Office (Medicare-Medicaid Coordination Office).  (No bill.)  Proposals related to the activities of the Federal Coordinated Health Care Office intended to improve the quality of care for recipients receiving benefits from both Medicare and Medicaid, i.e, dual-eligibles. 
</description>
         </specific_issues>
         <federal_agencies>U.S. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES, U.S. SENATE, Health &amp; Human Services - Dept of  (HHS), Centers For Medicare and  Medicaid Services  (CMS), Administration on Aging, Executive Office of the President (EOP)</federal_agencies>
         <lobbyists>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Max</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Richtman</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Dan</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Adcock</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Webster</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Phillips</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Diane</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Lifsey</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Brenda</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Sulick</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Julie</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Tippens</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition>Chief of Staff, Hon. Colleen Hanabusa</coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>Y</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
         </lobbyists>
         <foreign_entity_issues></foreign_entity_issues>
      </ali_info>
      <ali_info>
         <issueAreaCode>RET</issueAreaCode>
         <specific_issues>
            <description>Consumer Price Index for Elderly Consumers.  H.R. 649; H.R. 1030; S. 308; S. 567:  provisions establishing a consumer price index for elderly consumers (CPI-E) to compute cost-of-living adjustments (COLA) for Social Security benefits.  

Chained CPI.  (No bill).  Proposal to replace the current index used to calculate the Social Security COLA with a "chained CPI."</description>
            <description>Social Security Privatization.  (No bill.)  Proposals to convert Social Security to a system of private investment accounts.

Social Security Benefits.  (No bill.)  Provisions requiring progressive indexing, modifying COLAs, and increasing the Social Security retirement age.

Annual Social Security Statements.  (No bill.)  Restoration of mailing of annual Social Security statements to all workers.

Social Security Payroll Tax Cap.  S. 308; S. 500; S. 567; H.R. 1029; H.R. 1374; H.R. 649:  provisions raising the amount of wages subject to payroll taxes. 

Womens Social Security Improvements and Protections.  (No bill.)  Proposals to safeguard and improve benefit equity for women, including improving survivor benefits; to provide Social Security credits for caregiving; to enhance the special minimum benefit; to equalize rules for disabled and working widows; to restore student benefits; to improve benefits for disabled children; to strengthen the COLA; to increase the basic benefit; and to equalize benefits for same-sex married couples.

Social Security Equality. (No bill.)  Proposals to require the Social Security Administration to recognize same-sex marriage for the purposes of survivor, retirement and other benefits.

Social Security Administration Commissioner and Deputy Commissioner Appointments.  (No bill.)  Issues surrounding the impending leadership transition at the Social Security Administration.  

Social Security Benefits.  H.R. 1374:  provision to strengthen the Social Security special minimum benefit; increase benefits after 20 years of eligibility; reinstate the students benefit; and to increase the Social Security tax rate.

Immigration Reform.  (No bill.)  Proposals assuring that immigrants authorized to work as a result of immigration reform have access to all of their wages for the purpose of qualifying for Social Security benefits and reimbursing the Social Security trust funds for costs associated with immigration reform. 

Social Security Commission.  (No bill.)  Proposal to establish a commission that would develop policy options for restoring the Social Security program to solvency for the next 75 years, including fast-track authority for moving a bill recommending policy options through Congress. 
</description>
         </specific_issues>
         <federal_agencies>U.S. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES, U.S. SENATE, Vice President of the U.S., Social Security Administration (SSA), Administration on Aging</federal_agencies>
         <lobbyists>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Max</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Richtman</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Dan</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Adcock</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Webster</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Phillips</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Diane</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Lifsey</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Brenda</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Sulick</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Julie</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Tippens</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition>Chief of Staff, Hon. Colleen Hanabusa</coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>Y</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
         </lobbyists>
         <foreign_entity_issues></foreign_entity_issues>
      </ali_info>
      <ali_info>
         <issueAreaCode>TAX</issueAreaCode>
         <specific_issues>
            <description>Extension of Bush Era Tax Cuts.  H.R. 8 (112th Congress):  proposals to extend the Bush era tax cuts (P.L. 107-16, P.L. 108-27) to the first $250,000 of household income.

"The Corporate Tax Fairness Act of 2013."  S. 250:  proposals to end corporate tax breaks for shifting jobs and profits offshore.</description>
            <description>The American Family Economic Protection Act of 2013.  S. 388:  legislation to eliminate the automatic spending reductions scheduled to occur under current law (P.L. 112-25) for 2013; to partially eliminate the reductions scheduled for 2014; to eliminate or partially eliminate sequestration; and proposals to reduce the federal deficit, including a provision to ensure that taxpayers with annual income above $5 million face an average tax rate of at least 30 percent on their income.</description>
         </specific_issues>
         <federal_agencies>U.S. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES, U.S. SENATE</federal_agencies>
         <lobbyists>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Max</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Richtman</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Dan</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Adcock</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Webster</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Phillips</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Diane</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Lifsey</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Brenda</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Sulick</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Julie</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Tippens</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition>Chief of Staff, Hon. Colleen Hanabusa</coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>Y</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
         </lobbyists>
         <foreign_entity_issues></foreign_entity_issues>
      </ali_info>
   </alis>
   <updates>
      <clientAddress></clientAddress>
      <clientCity></clientCity>
      <clientState></clientState>
      <clientZip></clientZip>
      <clientZipext></clientZipext>
      <clientCountry></clientCountry>
      <prinClientCity></prinClientCity>
      <prinClientState></prinClientState>
      <prinClientZip></prinClientZip>
      <prinClientZipext></prinClientZipext>
      <prinClientCountry></prinClientCountry>
      <generalDescription></generalDescription>
      <inactive_lobbyists>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName>Michael</firstName>
            <lastName>Kibler</lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName></firstName>
            <lastName></lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName></firstName>
            <lastName></lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName></firstName>
            <lastName></lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName></firstName>
            <lastName></lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName></firstName>
            <lastName></lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName></firstName>
            <lastName></lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName></firstName>
            <lastName></lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
      </inactive_lobbyists>
      <inactive_ALIs>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
      </inactive_ALIs>
      <affiliatedUrl></affiliatedUrl>
      <affiliatedOrgs>
         <affiliatedOrg>
            <affiliatedOrgName></affiliatedOrgName>
            <affiliatedOrgAddress></affiliatedOrgAddress>
            <affiliatedOrgCity></affiliatedOrgCity>
            <affiliatedOrgState></affiliatedOrgState>
            <affiliatedOrgZip></affiliatedOrgZip>
            <affiliatedOrgCountry></affiliatedOrgCountry>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCity></affiliatedPrinOrgCity>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgState></affiliatedPrinOrgState>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCountry></affiliatedPrinOrgCountry>
         </affiliatedOrg>
         <affiliatedOrg>
            <affiliatedOrgName></affiliatedOrgName>
            <affiliatedOrgAddress></affiliatedOrgAddress>
            <affiliatedOrgCity></affiliatedOrgCity>
            <affiliatedOrgState></affiliatedOrgState>
            <affiliatedOrgZip></affiliatedOrgZip>
            <affiliatedOrgCountry></affiliatedOrgCountry>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCity></affiliatedPrinOrgCity>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgState></affiliatedPrinOrgState>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCountry></affiliatedPrinOrgCountry>
         </affiliatedOrg>
         <affiliatedOrg>
            <affiliatedOrgName></affiliatedOrgName>
            <affiliatedOrgAddress></affiliatedOrgAddress>
            <affiliatedOrgCity></affiliatedOrgCity>
            <affiliatedOrgState></affiliatedOrgState>
            <affiliatedOrgZip></affiliatedOrgZip>
            <affiliatedOrgCountry></affiliatedOrgCountry>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCity></affiliatedPrinOrgCity>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgState></affiliatedPrinOrgState>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCountry></affiliatedPrinOrgCountry>
         </affiliatedOrg>
         <affiliatedOrg>
            <affiliatedOrgName></affiliatedOrgName>
            <affiliatedOrgAddress></affiliatedOrgAddress>
            <affiliatedOrgCity></affiliatedOrgCity>
            <affiliatedOrgState></affiliatedOrgState>
            <affiliatedOrgZip></affiliatedOrgZip>
            <affiliatedOrgCountry></affiliatedOrgCountry>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCity></affiliatedPrinOrgCity>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgState></affiliatedPrinOrgState>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCountry></affiliatedPrinOrgCountry>
         </affiliatedOrg>
      </affiliatedOrgs>
      <inactiveOrgs>
         <inactiveOrgName></inactiveOrgName>
         <inactiveOrgName></inactiveOrgName>
         <inactiveOrgName></inactiveOrgName>
         <inactiveOrgName></inactiveOrgName>
         <inactiveOrgName></inactiveOrgName>
         <inactiveOrgName></inactiveOrgName>
      </inactiveOrgs>
      <foreignEntities>
         <foreignEntity>
            <name></name>
            <address></address>
            <city></city>
            <state></state>
            <country></country>
            <prinCity></prinCity>
            <prinState></prinState>
            <prinCountry></prinCountry>
            <contribution></contribution>
            <ownership_Percentage></ownership_Percentage>
         </foreignEntity>
         <foreignEntity>
            <name></name>
            <address></address>
            <city></city>
            <state></state>
            <country></country>
            <prinCity></prinCity>
            <prinState></prinState>
            <prinCountry></prinCountry>
            <contribution></contribution>
            <ownership_Percentage></ownership_Percentage>
         </foreignEntity>
      </foreignEntities>
      <inactive_ForeignEntities>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
      </inactive_ForeignEntities>
   </updates>
</LOBBYINGDISCLOSURE2>