<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl' href='../../ld2.xsl'?>
<LOBBYINGDISCLOSURE2>
   <imported>N</imported>
   <pages>11</pages>
   <submitURL></submitURL>
   <organizationName>MANUFACTURED HOUSING INSTITUTE</organizationName>
   <prefix></prefix>
   <firstName></firstName>
   <lastName></lastName>
   <registrantDifferentAddress>N</registrantDifferentAddress>
   <address1>2111 WILSON BOULEVARD, #100</address1>
   <address2></address2>
   <city>ARLINGTON</city>
   <state>VA</state>
   <zip>22201</zip>
   <zipext></zipext>
   <country>USA</country>
   <principal_city></principal_city>
   <principal_state></principal_state>
   <principal_zip></principal_zip>
   <principal_zipext></principal_zipext>
   <principal_country></principal_country>
   <selfSelect>Y</selfSelect>
   <clientName>MANUFACTURED HOUSING INSTITUTE</clientName>
   <clientGovtEntity>N</clientGovtEntity>
   <senateID>23714-12</senateID>
   <houseID>319660000</houseID>
   <reportYear>2013</reportYear>
   <reportType>Q1</reportType>
   <terminationDate></terminationDate>
   <noLobbying></noLobbying>
   <income></income>
   <expenses>161426.00</expenses>
   <expensesMethod>B</expensesMethod>
   <printedName>Laura M Lee, Controller &amp; VP - Finance &amp; Operations</printedName>
   <signedDate>04/12/2013</signedDate>
   <alis>
      <ali_info>
         <issueAreaCode>BAN</issueAreaCode>
         <specific_issues>
            <description>HR 1223 - GSE Credit Risk Equitable Treatment Act of 2011
HR 1224 - GSE Portfolio Risk Reduction Act of 2011
HR 1227 a bill to prohibit Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac from offering any new products during the term of any conservatorship or receivership of such enterprises</description>
            <description>HR. 1226 - A bill to repeal the affordable housing goals for Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac
HR 31 Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac Accountability and Transparency for Taxpayers
HR 1222 GSE Subsidy Elimination Act
H.R. 1221 - Equity in Government Compensation Act of 2011, to suspend the current compensation packages for the senior executives of Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac and establish compensation for such positions in accordance with rates of pay for senior employees in the Executive Branch of the Federal Government.
H.R. 1225 GSE Debt Issuance Approval Act of 2011 -To prohibit Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac from issuing any new debt without approval in advance by the Secretary of the Treasury
HR. 2441Housing Trust Fund Elimination Act of 2011 -To terminate the Housing Trust Fund and the requirement that Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac make annual allocations for such Fund. 
HR 463 Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac Transparency Act of 2011 -To apply the Freedom of Information Act to the Federal National Mortgage Association and the Federal Home Loan Mortgage Corporation during any period that such entities are in conservatorship or receivership.
H.R.2436 Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac Taxpayer Payback Act of 2011 -To prohibit any reduction in the rate of dividends paid to the Secretary of the Treasury on the senior preferred stock of Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac purchased by the Secretary. 
H.R.2439 Removing GSEs Charters During Receivership Act of 2011 - To amend the Federal Housing Enterprises Financial Safety and Soundness Act of 1992 to authorize the Federal Housing Finance Agency, as receiver of Fannie Mae or Freddie Mac, to revoke the charters of such enterprises or any limited-life regulated entity established under such receivership. 
H.R.2440 Market Transparency and Taxpayer Protection Act of 2011 -To protect the taxpayers of the United States by requiring Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac to sell or dispose of the assets of such enterprises that are not critical to their missions.
H.R.2462 Cap the GSE Bailout Act of 2011 - To limit the aggregate amount provided by the taxpayers of the United States for the bailout of Fannie Mae and Freddie Mac.
Dodd-Frank Wall Street Reform &amp; Consumer Protection Act - Public Law No: 111-203.  Implementation
H.R.2413 Secondary Market Facility for Residential Mortgages Act of 2011 - Establishes a Secondary Market Facility for Residential Mortgages as an instrumentality of the federal government, subject to supervision by the Federal Housing Finance Agency (FHFA) Board.
H.R.1859 Housing Finance Reform Act of 2011 - Amends the Federal Housing Enterprises Financial Safety and Soundness Act of 1992 to authorize the Director of the Federal Housing Finance Agency (FHFA) to: (1) provide for the organization, incorporation, examination, operation, and regulation of housing finance guaranty associations (which may be corporations, mutual associations, partnerships, limited liability corporations, cooperatives, or other appropriate organizational forms); and (2) issue charters for them.
</description>
         </specific_issues>
         <federal_agencies>U.S. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES</federal_agencies>
         <lobbyists>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Jason</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Boehlert</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Richard</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Jennison</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Kelli</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Nelson</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
         </lobbyists>
         <foreign_entity_issues></foreign_entity_issues>
      </ali_info>
      <ali_info>
         <issueAreaCode>ENG</issueAreaCode>
         <specific_issues>
            <description>S. 398 Implementation of a National Consensus Appliance Agreements - to improve the energy-efficiency of certain appliances and equipment
Mobile Home Replacement Program - To provide assitance to owners of manufactured homes contructed prior to 1976 to purchase Energy Star qualified manufactured homes.</description>
            <description>Energy Independence Security Act of 2007- Energy requirements for manufactured homes - The Department of Energy has initiated the drafting of proposed amendments to the energy requirements of the HUD Code homes as directed by EISA 2007.  
S. 1000 - the Energy Savings and Industrial Competitiveness Act - To promote energy savings in residential and commercial buildings and industry.
S.398 : Implementation of National Consensus Appliance Agreements Act - To amend the Energy Policy and Conservation Act to improve the energy efficiency of certain appliances and equipment.
S. 1813 (#1812) Renew the Energy Efficient Home Tax Credit (IRC 45L) beyond 2012.
S. 2204 the Repeal Big Oil Tax Subsidies Act - legislation would have extended the new energy efficient home tax credit.
</description>
         </specific_issues>
         <federal_agencies>U.S. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES, U.S. SENATE, Housing &amp; Urban Development - Dept of (HUD), Energy - Dept of, Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Office of Management &amp; Budget (OMB)</federal_agencies>
         <lobbyists>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Lois</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Starkey</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Jason</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Boehlert</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Kelli</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Nelson</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
         </lobbyists>
         <foreign_entity_issues></foreign_entity_issues>
      </ali_info>
      <ali_info>
         <issueAreaCode>FIN</issueAreaCode>
         <specific_issues>
            <description>Foreclosure Prevention Act - Comprehensive FHA Title I and Title II reform.  Net Operating Loss (NOL) carryback provisions, tax credit for homebuyers who purchase a home in foreclosure, provision allowing for an additional standard deduction for real property taxes for non-itemizers.</description>
            <description>HUD Proposed Rule - GSE Affordable Housing Goals-24 CFR Part 81-Proposed rule will establish the housing goals (effective 2009) for the GSEs.
HUD Proposed Rule - Reform of the Real Estate Procedures Act (RESPA)-24 CFR Parts 203 and 3500-Proposed rule would require lenders to itemize borrower costs on an enhanced Good Faith Estimate. Lenders to disclose Yield Spread Premiums paid to brokers.  New penalties for RESPA violations.
Federal Reserve Proposed Rule - Regulation Z Reform- 12CFR Part 226 Fed proposed defines "higher prices mortgage loans" (HPML as any loan with an APR 3pts above yield on t-bills with comparable terms.  Rules provides that HPML lenders required to consider borrower's ability to repay, verify income, escrow taxes and insurance, and are not permitted to use prepayment penalties
FHA Title II Morgagee Letter "Manufactured Housing Policy Guidance" - "Manufactured Housing Policy Guidance"-The letter covers a host of issues under the topic of property eligiblity and underwriting eligibility.  The letter indicates FHA's desire to receive invoices and supporting documentation for all site-work from installers and subcontractors.  This documentation is not required for site-built construction loans and is excessive considering all homes are appraised by FHA approved appraisers.
Dodd-Frank Wall Street Reform &amp; Consumer Protection Act - Public Law No: 111-203.  Implementation
H.R. 3849 and S. 3484, the Preserving Access to Manufactured Housing Act: The legislation would provide clarity and certainty to consumers and preserve the manufactured housing industry without any deterioration of important consumer protections. To amend the S.A.F.E. Mortgage Licensing Act of 2008 to provide an exception from the definition of loan originator for certain loans made with respect to manufactured homes, to amend the Truth in Lending Act to modify the definition of a high-cost mortgage, and for other purposes.
</description>
         </specific_issues>
         <federal_agencies>U.S. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES, U.S. SENATE, Housing &amp; Urban Development - Dept of (HUD), Treasury - Dept of, Small Business Adminstration (SBA)</federal_agencies>
         <lobbyists>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Jason</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Boehlert</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Richard</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Jennison</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Kelli</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Nelson</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
         </lobbyists>
         <foreign_entity_issues></foreign_entity_issues>
      </ali_info>
      <ali_info>
         <issueAreaCode>HOU</issueAreaCode>
         <specific_issues>
            <description>H.R. 175, the Smart Housing in Disasters Act of 2011. Amends the Robert T. Stafford Disaster Relief and Emergency Assistance Act. Directs the Administrator of FEMA to develop a lifecycle and tracking plan for housing units provided to individuals and households affected by an disaster.
H.R. 1209, Section 8 Voucher Reform Act.  To reform the housing voucher program under Section 8 of the US Housing Act of 1937</description>
            <description>24 CFR 3282, 3285-HUD On-Site Completion of Construction of Manufactured homes-Will set forth provisions under a new subpart allowing for the on-site completion of innovative homes components/construction practices that are essentially extensions of home construction elements currently covered by the HUD-Code but not expressly provided for and therefore require Alternative Construction letters. In addition including provisions for quality assurance programs, monitoring audits, and notifications.
24 CRF 3280.402-HUD-Code Truss Testing Protocol-The proposed rule would amend Sec.3280.402 to provide more stringent initial qualification of truss design.
HUD-Code 3282 Subpart E &amp; H- HUD has initiated a new effort directed at revising the regulations covering manufacturer inspection and certification requirements, and primary inspection agencies.
Residential Fire Sprinklers - The number of jurisdictions requiring the installation of fire sprinklers in single family home is likely to grow because of new residential fire sprinkler requirements in the International Code Council's 2009 edition of the International Residential Code.
Fiscal 2013 Appropriations - Federal Housing Administration - HUD
Subpart I HUD 24 CFR3282 to propose change to the manufactured home consumer complaint handling program.
24 CFT Part 3280  HUD proposed rule to make various changes to the manufactured housing construction safty standards
HUD - Implementation of new quality assurance quidelines and compliance programs and audits.
H.R. 1751 CJ's Home Protection Act - Amends the National Manufactured Housing Construction and Safety Standards Act of 1974 to require such standards to require each manufactured home delivered for sale to be supplied with a weather radio
H.R. 1309, the Flood Insurance Reform Act of 2011.  Terminating the National Flood Insurance Program
FHA Permanent Foundation Requirements for Manufactured Homes - 24 CRF 203.47f - In lieu of installing HUD Code homes in accordance with the Guide to Permanent Foundations, FHA will be proposing to adopt the HUD Model Installation Standard (or state equivalent) as its permanent foundation requirement
Interior and Environment Appropriations bill - Rehberg Amendment to withhold enforcement and implementation funding of EPA's Renovation, Repair &amp; Painting (RRP) until EPA approves a commercially available lead test kit that meets the criteria EPA specified in its regulation.
HUD-Reducing Regulatory Burden:  Retrospective Review Under Executive Order 13563, Improving Regulation and Regulatory Review.  MHI responded to HUD's Request for Public Comments.  
HUD-FHA (203)(b): Regulation, waiver for request for flood flame elevator requirement
Fiscal 2013 Appropriations - Department of Energy
FEMA Temporary Housing Units (THUs) - Lobbied FEMA for improvements for THU solication process and other recommendations for inproved disaster response and recovery
</description>
         </specific_issues>
         <federal_agencies>U.S. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES, U.S. SENATE, Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA), Housing &amp; Urban Development - Dept of (HUD)</federal_agencies>
         <lobbyists>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Lois</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Starkey</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Jason</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Boehlert</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Kelli</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Nelson</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
         </lobbyists>
         <foreign_entity_issues></foreign_entity_issues>
      </ali_info>
      <ali_info>
         <issueAreaCode>TAX</issueAreaCode>
         <specific_issues>
            <description>Extension of he ENERGY STAR tax credit which  expired in December 2011.  Currently, manufacturers who build ENERGY STAR homes are eligible to receive a $1,000 tax credit while modular builders receive a $2,000 by exceeding the IECC by 50%
Morgage Interest Deduction, Carried Interest  - As Congress and the Adminstration look at tax increases in light of deficit concerns
S. 1813, Amendment #1812 - Extends the Energy Star Tax Credit for manufactured and modular homes.</description>
         </specific_issues>
         <federal_agencies>U.S. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES, U.S. SENATE, Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), Treasury - Dept of</federal_agencies>
         <lobbyists>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Jason</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Boehlert</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Kelli</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Nelson</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
         </lobbyists>
         <foreign_entity_issues></foreign_entity_issues>
      </ali_info>
      <ali_info>
         <issueAreaCode>LBR</issueAreaCode>
         <specific_issues>
            <description>Employee Free Choice Act - The bills main provision would effectively eliminate the secret ballot for unions organizing elections and replace it with card check where the vote of workers would be made public to employers, co-workers and union organizers</description>
         </specific_issues>
         <federal_agencies>U.S. HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES, U.S. SENATE</federal_agencies>
         <lobbyists>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Jason</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Boehlert</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName>Kelli</lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName>Nelson</lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
            <lobbyist>
               <lobbyistFirstName></lobbyistFirstName>
               <lobbyistLastName></lobbyistLastName>
               <lobbyistSuffix></lobbyistSuffix>
               <coveredPosition></coveredPosition>
               <lobbyistNew>N</lobbyistNew>
            </lobbyist>
         </lobbyists>
         <foreign_entity_issues></foreign_entity_issues>
      </ali_info>
   </alis>
   <updates>
      <clientAddress></clientAddress>
      <clientCity></clientCity>
      <clientState></clientState>
      <clientZip></clientZip>
      <clientZipext></clientZipext>
      <clientCountry></clientCountry>
      <prinClientCity></prinClientCity>
      <prinClientState></prinClientState>
      <prinClientZip></prinClientZip>
      <prinClientZipext></prinClientZipext>
      <prinClientCountry></prinClientCountry>
      <generalDescription></generalDescription>
      <inactive_lobbyists>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName></firstName>
            <lastName></lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName></firstName>
            <lastName></lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName></firstName>
            <lastName></lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
         <inactive_lobbyist>
            <firstName></firstName>
            <lastName></lastName>
            <suffix></suffix>
         </inactive_lobbyist>
      </inactive_lobbyists>
      <inactive_ALIs>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
         <ali_Code></ali_Code>
      </inactive_ALIs>
      <affiliatedUrl></affiliatedUrl>
      <affiliatedOrgs>
         <affiliatedOrg>
            <affiliatedOrgName></affiliatedOrgName>
            <affiliatedOrgAddress></affiliatedOrgAddress>
            <affiliatedOrgCity></affiliatedOrgCity>
            <affiliatedOrgState></affiliatedOrgState>
            <affiliatedOrgZip></affiliatedOrgZip>
            <affiliatedOrgCountry></affiliatedOrgCountry>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCity></affiliatedPrinOrgCity>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgState></affiliatedPrinOrgState>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCountry></affiliatedPrinOrgCountry>
         </affiliatedOrg>
         <affiliatedOrg>
            <affiliatedOrgName></affiliatedOrgName>
            <affiliatedOrgAddress></affiliatedOrgAddress>
            <affiliatedOrgCity></affiliatedOrgCity>
            <affiliatedOrgState></affiliatedOrgState>
            <affiliatedOrgZip></affiliatedOrgZip>
            <affiliatedOrgCountry></affiliatedOrgCountry>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCity></affiliatedPrinOrgCity>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgState></affiliatedPrinOrgState>
            <affiliatedPrinOrgCountry></affiliatedPrinOrgCountry>
         </affiliatedOrg>
      </affiliatedOrgs>
      <inactiveOrgs>
         <inactiveOrgName></inactiveOrgName>
         <inactiveOrgName></inactiveOrgName>
         <inactiveOrgName></inactiveOrgName>
      </inactiveOrgs>
      <foreignEntities>
         <foreignEntity>
            <name></name>
            <address></address>
            <city></city>
            <state></state>
            <country></country>
            <prinCity></prinCity>
            <prinState></prinState>
            <prinCountry></prinCountry>
            <contribution></contribution>
            <ownership_Percentage></ownership_Percentage>
         </foreignEntity>
      </foreignEntities>
      <inactive_ForeignEntities>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
         <inactive_ForeignEntity></inactive_ForeignEntity>
      </inactive_ForeignEntities>
   </updates>
</LOBBYINGDISCLOSURE2>